<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on SMN Robotics</title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on SMN Robotics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About FIRST</title>
      <link>/about/about-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about-first/</guid>
      <description>This is the FIRST definition from the FIRST website
&amp;ldquo;Founded in 1989 by inventor Dean Kamen, FIRST® (For Inspiration and Recognition of Science and Technology) is a global nonprofit (501(c)(3)) organization that prepares young people for the future through a suite of inclusive, team-based robotics programs for ages 4-18 (PreK-12). Our programs are suitable for schools or structured afterschool activities and receive support from a vast network of volunteers, educators, and sponsors/donors, including over 200 Fortune 500 companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about-us/</guid>
      <description>We are Shawnee Mission North&amp;rsquo;s FRC (First Robotics Competition) team, Our team number is 937, which means we were one of the first 1000&amp;rsquo;s teams to join the FRC family. Our club was started in 2002 with the name &amp;ldquo;The North Stars&amp;rdquo;. One of the first Mentors was Bill Kirchner, who at the time was the Robotics teacher at SMN. The first competition our team competed in was in St. Louis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Join</title>
      <link>/about/how-to-join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/how-to-join/</guid>
      <description>Hello, This is how YOU can join robotics team 937. This school year 24&amp;rsquo;-25&amp;rsquo; our freshman first meeting is on September 9th! This meeting will be like an open house! it&amp;rsquo;ll start at 3:10 after school and end at 5:30 pm in room 183. This will be filled with fun team activities and general information about the club, also you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be a freshman to join! No matter what grade you are you can come join us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specialty</title>
      <link>/about/subteams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/subteams/</guid>
      <description>President
Quinn
Vice-President
Malachi
Mechanical
Silas
Malachi
Ellie
Programming
Quinn
Jack
Marz
Power Distribution
Brayden
Max
Jorden
Marketing
Zabby
Juliany
Zander
Marz</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
